<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thomas Brugman</title><link>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Thomas Brugman</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>January Updates</title><link>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/posts/2025/january-updates/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/posts/2025/january-updates/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="recent-changes-and-updates">Recent Changes and Updates&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In the last month of 2024, we saw some significant changes to our projects and workflows. Here&amp;rsquo;s a summary of the key updates:&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="github-workflow-improvements">GitHub Workflow Improvements&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Our Arch Linux ISO building workflow received a major overhaul, introducing several improvements:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Enhanced caching system for Pacman packages, reducing build times by ~30%&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Improved error handling and logging&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Automated release notes generation&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SHA256 and SHA512 checksums for all releases&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="website-enhancements">Website Enhancements&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The website has received several improvements:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>GitHub Workflow Rewrite for Arch Linux without the beeps</title><link>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/posts/2024/arch-linux-without-the-beeps-gh-wf-overhaul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/posts/2024/arch-linux-without-the-beeps-gh-wf-overhaul/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="the-github-workflow-rewrite">The GitHub Workflow Rewrite&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Today, I&amp;rsquo;d like to share how we&amp;rsquo;ve improved the GitHub Actions workflow for automatically building our Arch Linux ISO without system beeps. This workflow is a crucial component of our project, as it generates a fresh ISO with the latest updates daily.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="key-improvements">Key Improvements&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Robust Error Handling&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Addition of comprehensive error checking&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Improved logging for debugging&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Timeout limit of 120 minutes to prevent hanging builds&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Additional Details&lt;/strong>: The error handling now includes specific checks for common issues such as network failures and package conflicts, ensuring that the build process is more resilient.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Automated Release Notes&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Removing Some Unused Projects</title><link>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/posts/2024/removing-some-unused-projects/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/posts/2024/removing-some-unused-projects/</guid><description>&lt;p>I would like to announce that I will be removing several inactive projects from my GitHub account. After reviewing my repositories, I&amp;rsquo;ve identified projects that are no longer being maintained or used.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Projects being removed:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Archcraft&lt;/strong> (&lt;a href="https://github.com/Githubguy132010/archcraft">GitHub&lt;/a>)&lt;br>
A fork intended to replicate Arch Linux modifications without audio signals. (Arch Linux without the beeps)&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Reason for removal:&lt;/strong> Lack of development progress.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Vanilla-OS-image&lt;/strong> (&lt;a href="https://github.com/Githubguy132010/VanillaOS-image">GitHub&lt;/a>)&lt;br>
A repo for a custom VanillaOS image that I was working on.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Welcome to My Digital Space</title><link>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/about/who-i-am/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 18:11:49 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/about/who-i-am/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="hi-im-thomas-">Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Thomas ðŸ‘‹&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A Linux enthusiast and hobby developer from the Netherlands with a passion for automation and open source. I have several years of experience tinkering with Linux systems, configuring servers, and developing small-scale applications. My passion lies in finding efficient solutions to technical challenges and automating repetitive tasks. I specialize in:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>ðŸ§ Linux System Configuration: Extensive experience with various Linux distributions, including Arch Linux, Debian, and Ubuntu. Proficient in system administration, package management, and troubleshooting.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>ðŸ”§ Shell Scripting (Bash): Skilled in writing Bash scripts to automate system tasks, manage files, and process data.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>âš™ï¸ Infrastructure as Code (YAML): Experience with using YAML for configuration management and infrastructure automation, particularly with tools like Ansible and Docker Compose.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>ðŸ¤– GitHub Actions Automation: Proficient in creating and managing CI/CD pipelines using GitHub Actions to automate software builds, testing, and deployment.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>ðŸ–¥ï¸ WSL Development: Experienced in setting up and utilizing Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) for a seamless development experience across Windows and Linux environments.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Feel free to explore my &lt;a href="https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/projects">projects&lt;/a> to see some of my work. If you have any questions or would like to connect, don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to reach out via the &lt;a href="https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/contact">contact&lt;/a> page.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>