<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thomas Brugman</title>
    <link>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Thomas Brugman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>January Updates</title>
      <link>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/posts/2025/january-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/posts/2025/january-updates/</guid>
      <description>Recent Changes and Updates In the last month of 2024, we saw some significant changes to our projects and workflows. Here&amp;rsquo;s a summary of the key updates:&#xA;GitHub Workflow Improvements Our Arch Linux ISO building workflow received a major overhaul, introducing several improvements:&#xA;Enhanced caching system for Pacman packages, reducing build times by ~30% Improved error handling and logging Automated release notes generation SHA256 and SHA512 checksums for all releases Website Enhancements The website has received several improvements:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Workflow Rewrite for Arch Linux without the beeps</title>
      <link>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/posts/2024/arch-linux-without-the-beeps-gh-wf-overhaul/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/posts/2024/arch-linux-without-the-beeps-gh-wf-overhaul/</guid>
      <description>The GitHub Workflow Rewrite Today, I&amp;rsquo;d like to share how we&amp;rsquo;ve improved the GitHub Actions workflow for automatically building our Arch Linux ISO without system beeps. This workflow is a crucial component of our project, as it generates a fresh ISO with the latest updates daily.&#xA;Key Improvements Robust Error Handling&#xA;Addition of comprehensive error checking Improved logging for debugging Timeout limit of 120 minutes to prevent hanging builds Additional Details: The error handling now includes specific checks for common issues such as network failures and package conflicts, ensuring that the build process is more resilient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Removing Some Unused Projects</title>
      <link>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/posts/2024/removing-some-unused-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/posts/2024/removing-some-unused-projects/</guid>
      <description>I would like to announce that I will be removing several inactive projects from my GitHub account. After reviewing my repositories, I&amp;rsquo;ve identified projects that are no longer being maintained or used.&#xA;Projects being removed:&#xA;Archcraft (GitHub)&#xA;A fork intended to replicate Arch Linux modifications without audio signals. (Arch Linux without the beeps)&#xA;Reason for removal: Lack of development progress. Vanilla-OS-image (GitHub)&#xA;A repo for a custom VanillaOS image that I was working on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to My Digital Space</title>
      <link>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/about/who-i-am/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 18:11:49 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GitHubguy132010.github.io/about/who-i-am/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Thomas 👋 A Linux enthusiast and hobby developer from the Netherlands with a passion for automation and open source. I have several years of experience tinkering with Linux systems, configuring servers, and developing small-scale applications. My passion lies in finding efficient solutions to technical challenges and automating repetitive tasks. I specialize in:&#xA;🐧 Linux System Configuration: Extensive experience with various Linux distributions, including Arch Linux, Debian, and Ubuntu. Proficient in system administration, package management, and troubleshooting.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
