<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on Thomas Brugman</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on Thomas Brugman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 18:11:49 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to My Digital Space</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/who-i-am/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 18:11:49 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/who-i-am/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;hi-im-thomas-&#34;&gt;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Thomas 👋&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Linux enthusiast and hobby developer from the Netherlands with a passion for automation and open source. I have several years of experience tinkering with Linux systems, configuring servers, and developing small-scale applications. My passion lies in finding efficient solutions to technical challenges and automating repetitive tasks. I specialize in:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🐧 Linux System Configuration: Extensive experience with various Linux distributions, including Arch Linux, Debian, and Ubuntu. Proficient in system administration, package management, and troubleshooting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🔧 Shell Scripting (Bash): Skilled in writing Bash scripts to automate system tasks, manage files, and process data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⚙️ Infrastructure as Code (YAML): Experience with using YAML for configuration management and infrastructure automation, particularly with tools like Ansible and Docker Compose.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🤖 GitHub Actions Automation: Proficient in creating and managing CI/CD pipelines using GitHub Actions to automate software builds, testing, and deployment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🖥️ WSL Development: Experienced in setting up and utilizing Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) for a seamless development experience across Windows and Linux environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to explore my &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/projects&#34;&gt;projects&lt;/a&gt; to see some of my work. If you have any questions or would like to connect, don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to reach out via the &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact&#34;&gt;contact&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
